The solution is to override the onPostExecute method
of the AsyncTask. And this runs on the main
thread. We received the string array of forecast results,
which came as a return value from the do
in background method above. First, we clear the ForecastAdapter
of all the previous forecast entries. Then we go
ahead and add each new forecast entry one by
one to the ForecastAdapter. This is what ultimately triggers
the listView to update. Note that if you're targeting Honeycomb
devices and above, you can use an addAll method here,
so you don't have to add them one by one.
You can just add it once and update the listView once.
Once you hit Refresh, you'll see the weather forecast for
the next seven days for your location. Even though we hit
Refresh, we don't have any verbose logging statements being printed
out here. We don't need them anymore, because we have a
way to check that our code is correct by looking at the UI now.